# **JEREMY CRUMP**

http://jeremycrump.work

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm currently enrolled at MATC studying Web and Software Development.

Web development is an exciting and fulfilling experience. After 10 years of working as a chef in the restaurant industry I have acquired swift critical thinking skills and team mentality required to be successful in the ever growing technology field. The surplus of knowledge to gain, problem solving scenarios, and the creative aspects of software and web development are just a few examples of the things I love about this industry.

## WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSES

Sept. 2019 - Dec. 2019 Udemy - The Complete Javascript Course 2020 - Jonas Schmedtman

Studied Asynchronous JavaScript, DOM manipulation, and ES6 basic fundamentals.

Also, gained basic knowledge of NPM, Babel, nodeJS, and Webpack.

Jan. 2019 - Sept. 2019 FreeCodeCamp

Studied Basic JavaScript ES5 fundamentals. Studied HTML 5 and CSS. Learned how to make websites responsive for mobile devices using media queries. Built static web

forms. Created a base portfolio using CSS flexbox.

#### **SKILLS**

NETBEANS C#
SQL
JAVA

VISUAL STUDIO JAVASCRIPT
VISUAL STUDIO CODE HTML5

#### **EDUCATION**

Aug 2020 - Present Milwaukee Area Technical College

**CSS** 

A.A.S - IT WEB/SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

### **EMPLOYMENT**

Feb. 2016 - Apr. 2018 Odd Duck Restaurant · Sous Chef · Milwaukee

Mar. 2010 - Oct. 2014 Longman & Eagle · Tournant Chef · Chicago , IL

I worked the line for all stations in a high volume Michelin starred restaurant for brunch and dinner service. I helped prepare locally sourced dinner for over 80 guests at the Outstanding in the Field event at City Farm in July 2013. I ensured all dishes met taste, temperature and presentation standards. I also performed safety and sanitation procedures. Additionally, I assisted line cooks and chefs with daily tasks prior to dinner service.